water4.org 2017-08-04

# Privacy Policy - Water4

## We Care About Your Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices. This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on our website. By using this website, you consent to the use of information that you provide us in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  Please note that this policy is subject to change. 

## The Information We Collect And How We Use It

In operating our website, we may collect and process the following personal data or information about you:

  * If you make a donation to Water4, we will request personally identifiable information about you, such as your name, address, phone number, credit card/debit  information, and email address.  We request such information to facilitate your donation and communicate with you about it.  In addition, we may use this information to update you periodically on the work being conducted by Water4 and/or to provide you with information regarding events.  We may also use this information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, and to answer any questions you might have.
  * When you choose to participate in various fundraising or awareness campaigns for Water4, we may request additional information including, but not limited to, your name, an image or photography, contact information, and narratives authored by you.  By choosing to provide any of this information, you are explicitly granting Water4 permission to use any provided information for public use, posting, and consumption.
  * Water4 does not sell or rent our donor lists to anyone.  We also do not share your personal data with any third parties other than service providers we employ to perform functions on our behalf, such as sending email updates, direct mail, processing credit card payments and organizing events specifically designed to keep you abreast of Water4 activities.  These companies and individuals have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but are not authorized to use it for any other purpose.

## Links To Third Party Websites And Third-Party Applications

To allow you to interact with third-party websites on which you may have accounts (such as social media websites) or join communities on such websites, we may provide links or embed third-party applications that allow you to login, post content, or join communities from our websites. We may also provide you with general links to third-party web sites. Your use of these links and applications is subject to the third-parties’ privacy policies, and you should become familiar with the third-parties’ privacy policies before using the links or applications. 

Water4 is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those third-party websites.

## Children's Privacy 

Protecting the privacy of young children is extremely important.  For that reason, we do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information to us or our website. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please [contact us](http://water4.org/contact/). 

## Our Commitment To Data Security 

We care about the security of your personal data and we employ commercially suitable physical, electronic, and managerial security techniques and procedures to safeguard and protect your personally identifiable information from unauthorized access by users inside and outside of the organization, including encrypting financial donations using SSL.  You should be aware, however, that no transmission of data over the Internet is 100% secure and that unauthorized third parties may unlawfully intercept or access private data.  You provide us with this information at your own risk. 

## How To Contact Us 

Your privacy is important to Water4, if you have any questions or concerns regarding Water4’s Privacy Policy, please contact us at: 

Water4  
P.O. Box 63  
Oklahoma City, OK 73101 

Phone:  (405) 551-8214

Or email us at:  [info@water4.org](mailto:info@water4.org) 

We would like to thank our donors for selecting Water4 and are grateful for the donations that help us sustain our work and services toward eradicating the global water crisis, and we would also like to thank our visitors for taking the time to understand more about our cause by browsing our website.
